[Applause]
they say
health is wealth unfortunately it is
true when you fall ill
a study revealed that medical inflation
in india is likely to rise at 10 percent
so by 10 years the cost of heart surgery
would be two and a half times more than
today
studies conducted in 2016 reveals that
approximately 20 lakh people suffer from
heart attack
every year 25
of death occurs in the age group of 25
to 29 years
one person is killed due to heart attack
every 33 seconds
and above four crore indians suffer from
heart disease in india
if you don't have a sufficient amount to
pay medical bills in your savings
account
which is a better option break your
long-term investments
or sell your home or gold borrow money
from relatives or friends
buy a health insurance policy
[Music]
your decision to buy sufficient health
insurance cover will protect and secure
your loved ones
today and tomorrow to buy the best
policy suitable to your needs
act now insurance is a subject matter of
[Music]
solicitation
you